<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<catalog>
    <movie id="6751668">
        <top-250-rank>30</top-250-rank>
        <title>Parasite</title>
        <runtimes>132</runtimes>
        <year>2019</year>
        <rating>8.6</rating>
        <votes>576390</votes>
        <description>The Kims - mother and father Chung-sook and Ki-taek, and their young adult offspring, son Ki-woo and daughter Ki-jung - are a poor family living in a shabby and cramped half basement apartment in a busy lower working class commercial district of Seoul. Without even knowing it, they, especially Mr. and Mrs. Kim, literally smell of poverty. Often as a collective, they perpetrate minor scams to get by, and even when they have jobs, they do the minimum work required. Ki-woo is the one who has dreams of getting out of poverty by one day going to university. Despite not having that university education, Ki-woo is chosen by his university student friend Min, who is leaving to go to school, to take over his tutoring job to Park Da-hye, who Min plans to date once he returns to Seoul and she herself is in university. The Parks are a wealthy family who for four years have lived in their modernistic house designed by and the former residence of famed architect Namgoong. While Mr. and Mrs. Park are all about status, Mrs. Park has a flighty, simpleminded mentality and temperament, which Min tells Ki-woo to feel comfortable in lying to her about his education to get the job. In getting the job, Ki-woo further learns that Mrs. Park is looking for an art therapist for the Parks' adolescent son, Da-song, Ki-woo quickly recommending his professional art therapist friend "Jessica", really Ki-jung who he knows can pull off the scam in being the easiest liar of the four Kims. In Ki-woo also falling for Da-hye, he begins to envision himself in that house, and thus the Kims as a collective start a plan for all the Kims, like Ki-jung using assumed names, to replace existing servants in the Parks' employ in orchestrating reasons for them to be fired. The most difficult to get rid of may be Moon-gwang, the Parks' housekeeper who literally came with the house - she Namgoong's housekeeper when he lived there - and thus knows all the little nooks and crannies of it better than the Parks themselves. The question then becomes how far the Kims can take this scam in their quest to become their version of the Parks.</description>
        <cover-url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYWZjMjk3ZTItODQ2ZC00NTY5LWE0ZDYtZTI3MjcwN2Q5NTVkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODk4OTc3MTY@._V1_SY150_CR0,0,101,150_.jpg</cover-url>
        <genres>
            <item>Comedy</item>
            <item>Drama</item>
            <item>Thriller</item>
        </genres>
        <director>
            <person id="94435">
                <name>Bong Joon Ho</name>
            </person>
        </director>
        <cast>
            <person id="814280">
                <name>Kang-ho Song</name>
            </person>
            <person id="1310525">
                <name>Lee Sun-kyun</name>
            </person>
            <person id="1856097">
                <name>Cho Yeo-jeong</name>
            </person>
            <person id="6079248">
                <name>Choi Woo-sik</name>
            </person>
            <person id="6476224">
                <name>Park So-dam</name>
            </person>
        </cast>
        <countries>
            <item>South Korea</item>
        </countries>
    </movie>
    <movie id="8503618">
        <top-250-rank>59</top-250-rank>
        <title>Hamilton</title>
        <runtimes>160</runtimes>
        <year>2020</year>
        <rating>8.5</rating>
        <votes>59794</votes>
        <description>"Hamilton" is the story of America then, told by America now. Featuring a score that blends hip-hop, jazz, RB, and show tunes, "Hamilton" has taken the story of American founding father Alexander Hamilton and created a revolutionary moment in theater--a musical that has had a profound impact on culture, politics, and education. Captured at the Richard Rodgers Theater on Broadway in June 2016, the film transports its audience into the world of the Broadway show in a uniquely intimate way.</description>
        <cover-url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjViNWRjYWEtZTI0NC00N2E3LTk0NGQtMjY4NTM3OGNkZjY0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjUxMTY3ODM@._V1_SY150_CR0,0,101,150_.jpg</cover-url>
        <genres>
            <item>Biography</item>
            <item>Drama</item>
            <item>History</item>
            <item>Musical</item>
        </genres>
        <director>
            <person id="2371802">
                <name>Thomas Kail</name>
            </person>
        </director>
        <cast>
            <person id="4377526">
                <name>Daveed Diggs</name>
            </person>
            <person id="325989">
                <name>Renée Elise Goldsberry</name>
            </person>
            <person id="2676147">
                <name>Jonathan Groff</name>
            </person>
            <person id="1862960">
                <name>Chris Jackson</name>
            </person>
            <person id="5093499">
                <name>Jasmine Cephas Jones</name>
            </person>
        </cast>
        <countries>
            <item>United States</item>
        </countries>
    </movie>
    <movie id="7286456">
        <top-250-rank>61</top-250-rank>
        <title>Joker</title>
        <runtimes>122</runtimes>
        <year>2019</year>
        <rating>8.4</rating>
        <votes>963051</votes>
        <description>Arthur Fleck works as a clown and is an aspiring stand-up comic. He has mental health issues, part of which involves uncontrollable laughter. Times are tough and, due to his issues and occupation, Arthur has an even worse time than most. Over time these issues bear down on him, shaping his actions, making him ultimately take on the persona he is more known as...Joker.</description>
        <cover-url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNGVjNWI4ZGUtNzE0MS00YTJmLWE0ZDctN2ZiYTk2YmI3NTYyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTkxNjUyNQ@@._V1_SY150_CR0,0,101,150_.jpg</cover-url>
        <genres>
            <item>Crime</item>
            <item>Drama</item>
            <item>Thriller</item>
        </genres>
        <director>
            <person id="680846">
                <name>Todd Phillips</name>
            </person>
        </director>
        <cast>
            <person id="1618">
                <name>Joaquin Phoenix</name>
            </person>
            <person id="134">
                <name>Robert De Niro</name>
            </person>
            <person id="5939164">
                <name>Zazie Beetz</name>
            </person>
            <person id="175814">
                <name>Frances Conroy</name>
            </person>
            <person id="191442">
                <name>Brett Cullen</name>
            </person>
        </cast>
        <countries>
            <item>United States</item>
            <item>Canada</item>
        </countries>
    </movie>
    <movie id="4154756">
        <top-250-rank>64</top-250-rank>
        <title>Avengers: Infinity War</title>
        <runtimes>149</runtimes>
        <year>2018</year>
        <rating>8.4</rating>
        <votes>849829</votes>
        <description>As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too large for any one hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows: Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to collect all six Infinity Stones, artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will on all of reality. Everything the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment, the fate of Earth and existence has never been more uncertain.</description>
        <cover-url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjMxNjY2MDU1OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzY1MTUwNTM@._V1_SY150_CR0,0,101,150_.jpg</cover-url>
        <genres>
            <item>Action</item>
            <item>Adventure</item>
            <item>Sci-Fi</item>
        </genres>
        <director>
            <person id="751577">
                <name>Anthony Russo</name>
            </person>
            <person id="751648">
                <name>Joe Russo</name>
            </person>
        </director>
        <cast>
            <person id="375">
                <name>Robert Downey Jr.</name>
            </person>
            <person id="1165110">
                <name>Chris Hemsworth</name>
            </person>
            <person id="749263">
                <name>Mark Ruffalo</name>
            </person>
            <person id="262635">
                <name>Chris Evans</name>
            </person>
            <person id="424060">
                <name>Scarlett Johansson</name>
            </person>
        </cast>
        <countries>
            <item>United States</item>
        </countries>
    </movie>
    <movie id="4633694">
        <top-250-rank>68</top-250-rank>
        <title>Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse</title>
        <runtimes>117</runtimes>
        <year>2018</year>
        <rating>8.4</rating>
        <votes>385077</votes>
        <description>Phil Lord and Christopher Miller, the creative minds behind The Lego Movie and 21 Jump Street, bring their unique talents to a fresh vision of a different Spider-Man Universe, with a groundbreaking visual style that's the first of its kind. "Spider-Man(TM): Into the Spider-Verse" introduces Brooklyn teen Miles Morales (Shameik Moore), and the limitless possibilities of the Spider-Verse, where more than one can wear the mask.</description>
        <cover-url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjMwNDkxMTgzOF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTkwNTQ3NjM@._V1_SY150_CR0,0,101,150_.jpg</cover-url>
        <genres>
            <item>Animation</item>
            <item>Action</item>
            <item>Adventure</item>
            <item>Family</item>
            <item>Sci-Fi</item>
        </genres>
        <director>
            <person id="2130108">
                <name>Bob Persichetti</name>
            </person>
            <person id="709056">
                <name>Peter Ramsey</name>
            </person>
            <person id="745247">
                <name>Rodney Rothman</name>
            </person>
        </director>
        <cast>
            <person id="4271336">
                <name>Shameik Moore</name>
            </person>
            <person id="2159926">
                <name>Jake Johnson</name>
            </person>
            <person id="2794962">
                <name>Hailee Steinfeld</name>
            </person>
            <person id="991810">
                <name>Mahershala Ali</name>
            </person>
            <person id="3109964">
                <name>Brian Tyree Henry</name>
            </person>
        </cast>
        <countries>
            <item>United States</item>
        </countries>
    </movie>
    <movie id="4154796">
        <top-250-rank>76</top-250-rank>
        <title>Avengers: Endgame</title>
        <runtimes>181</runtimes>
        <year>2019</year>
        <rating>8.4</rating>
        <votes>833236</votes>
        <description>After the devastating events of Avengers: Infinity War (2018), the universe is in ruins due to the efforts of the Mad Titan, Thanos. With the help of remaining allies, the Avengers must assemble once more in order to undo Thanos's actions and undo the chaos to the universe, no matter what consequences may be in store, and no matter who they face...</description>
        <cover-url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTc5MDE2ODcwNV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzI2NzQ2NzM@._V1_SY150_CR0,0,101,150_.jpg</cover-url>
        <genres>
            <item>Action</item>
            <item>Adventure</item>
            <item>Drama</item>
            <item>Sci-Fi</item>
        </genres>
        <director>
            <person id="751577">
                <name>Anthony Russo</name>
            </person>
            <person id="751648">
                <name>Joe Russo</name>
            </person>
        </director>
        <cast>
            <person id="375">
                <name>Robert Downey Jr.</name>
            </person>
            <person id="262635">
                <name>Chris Evans</name>
            </person>
            <person id="749263">
                <name>Mark Ruffalo</name>
            </person>
            <person id="1165110">
                <name>Chris Hemsworth</name>
            </person>
            <person id="424060">
                <name>Scarlett Johansson</name>
            </person>
        </cast>
        <countries>
            <item>United States</item>
        </countries>
    </movie>
    <movie id="8267604">
        <top-250-rank>77</top-250-rank>
        <title>Capernaum</title>
        <runtimes>126</runtimes>
        <year>2018</year>
        <rating>8.4</rating>
        <votes>65213</votes>
        <description>Capernaüm ("Chaos") tells the story of Zain (Zain al-Rafeea), a Lebanese boy who sues his parents for the "crime" of giving him life. The film follows Zain as he journeys from gutsy, streetwise child to hardened 12-year-old "adult" fleeing his negligent parents, surviving through his wits on the streets, where he meets Ethiopian migrant worker Rahil, who provides him with shelter and food, as Zain takes care of her baby son Yonas in return. Zain later gets jailed for committing a violent crime, and finally seeks justice in a courtroom.</description>
        <cover-url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMmExNzU2ZWMtYzUwYi00YmM2LTkxZTQtNmVhNjY0NTMyMWI2XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTMxODk2OTU@._V1_SY150_CR0,0,101,150_.jpg</cover-url>
        <genres>
            <item>Drama</item>
        </genres>
        <director>
            <person id="1701024">
                <name>Nadine Labaki</name>
            </person>
        </director>
        <cast>
            <person id="9862858">
                <name>Zain Al Rafeea</name>
            </person>
            <person id="9862859">
                <name>Yordanos Shiferaw</name>
            </person>
            <person id="9862860">
                <name>Boluwatife Treasure Bankole</name>
            </person>
            <person id="10201625">
                <name>Kawsar Al Haddad</name>
            </person>
            <person id="5765775">
                <name>Fadi Yousef</name>
            </person>
        </cast>
        <countries>
            <item>Lebanon</item>
            <item>United States</item>
            <item>France</item>
            <item>Cyprus</item>
            <item>Qatar</item>
            <item>United Kingdom</item>
        </countries>
    </movie>
    <movie id="8579674">
        <top-250-rank>108</top-250-rank>
        <title>1917</title>
        <runtimes>119</runtimes>
        <year>2019</year>
        <rating>8.3</rating>
        <votes>442199</votes>
        <description>April 1917, the Western Front. Two British soldiers are sent to deliver an urgent message to an isolated regiment. If the message is not received in time the regiment will walk into a trap and be massacred. To get to the regiment they will need to cross through enemy territory. Time is of the essence and the journey will be fraught with danger.</description>
        <cover-url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOTdmNTFjNDEtNzg0My00ZjkxLTg1ZDAtZTdkMDc2ZmFiNWQ1XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTAzNzgwNTg@._V1_SX101_CR0,0,101,150_.jpg</cover-url>
        <genres>
            <item>Drama</item>
            <item>Thriller</item>
            <item>War</item>
        </genres>
        <director>
            <person id="5222">
                <name>Sam Mendes</name>
            </person>
        </director>
        <cast>
            <person id="2835616">
                <name>Dean-Charles Chapman</name>
            </person>
            <person id="1126657">
                <name>George MacKay</name>
            </person>
            <person id="990547">
                <name>Daniel Mays</name>
            </person>
            <person id="147">
                <name>Colin Firth</name>
            </person>
            <person id="2553988">
                <name>Pip Carter</name>
            </person>
        </cast>
        <countries>
            <item>United States</item>
            <item>United Kingdom</item>
            <item>India</item>
            <item>Spain</item>
            <item>Canada</item>
            <item>China</item>
        </countries>
    </movie>
    <movie id="6966692">
        <top-250-rank>125</top-250-rank>
        <title>Green Book</title>
        <runtimes>130</runtimes>
        <year>2018</year>
        <rating>8.2</rating>
        <votes>389500</votes>
        <description>In 1962, Tony "Tony Lip" Vallelonga, a tough bouncer, is looking for work when his nightclub is closed for renovations. The most promising offer turns out to be the driver for the African-American classical pianist Don Shirley for a concert tour into the Deep South states. Although hardly enthused at working for a black man, Tony accepts the job and they begin their trek armed with The Negro Motorist Green Book, a travel guide for safe travel through America's racial segregation. Together, the snobbishly erudite pianist and the crudely practical bouncer can barely get along with their clashing attitudes to life and ideals. However, as the disparate pair witness and endure America's appalling injustices on the road, they find a newfound respect for each other's talents and start to face them together. In doing so, they would nurture a friendship and understanding that would change both their lives.</description>
        <cover-url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYzIzYmJlYTYtNGNiYy00N2EwLTk4ZjItMGYyZTJiOTVkM2RlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODY1NDk1NjE@._V1_SX101_CR0,0,101,150_.jpg</cover-url>
        <genres>
            <item>Biography</item>
            <item>Comedy</item>
            <item>Drama</item>
            <item>Music</item>
        </genres>
        <director>
            <person id="268380">
                <name>Peter Farrelly</name>
            </person>
        </director>
        <cast>
            <person id="1557">
                <name>Viggo Mortensen</name>
            </person>
            <person id="991810">
                <name>Mahershala Ali</name>
            </person>
            <person id="4802">
                <name>Linda Cardellini</name>
            </person>
            <person id="1724319">
                <name>Sebastian Maniscalco</name>
            </person>
            <person id="1221253">
                <name>Dimiter D. Marinov</name>
            </person>
        </cast>
        <countries>
            <item>United States</item>
            <item>China</item>
        </countries>
    </movie>
    <movie id="4729430">
        <top-250-rank>164</top-250-rank>
        <title>Klaus</title>
        <runtimes>96</runtimes>
        <year>2019</year>
        <rating>8.2</rating>
        <votes>108385</votes>
        <description>When Jesper (Jason Schwartzman) distinguishes himself as the postal academy's worst student, he is stationed on a frozen island above the Arctic Circle, where the feuding locals hardly exchange words let alone letters. Jesper is about to give up when he finds an ally in local teacher Alva (Rashida Jones), and discovers Klaus (Oscar® winner J.K. Simmons), a mysterious carpenter who lives alone in a cabin full of handmade toys. These unlikely friendships return laughter to Smeerensburg, forging a new legacy of generous neighbors, magical lore and stockings hung by the chimney with care. An animated Christmas comedy directed by Despicable Me co-creator Sergio Pablos, KLAUS co-stars Rashida Jones, Jason Schwartzman and JK Simmons.</description>
        <cover-url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMWYwOThjM2ItZGYxNy00NTQwLWFlZWEtM2MzM2Q5MmY3NDU5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTkxNjUyNQ@@._V1_SY150_CR0,0,101,150_.jpg</cover-url>
        <genres>
            <item>Animation</item>
            <item>Adventure</item>
            <item>Comedy</item>
            <item>Family</item>
        </genres>
        <director>
            <person id="655053">
                <name>Sergio Pablos</name>
            </person>
            <person id="3582089">
                <name>Carlos Martínez López</name>
            </person>
        </director>
        <cast>
            <person id="5403">
                <name>Jason Schwartzman</name>
            </person>
            <person id="799777">
                <name>J.K. Simmons</name>
            </person>
            <person id="429069">
                <name>Rashida Jones</name>
            </person>
            <person id="766005">
                <name>Will Sasso</name>
            </person>
            <person id="10520267">
                <name>Neda Margrethe Labba</name>
            </person>
        </cast>
        <countries>
            <item>Spain</item>
            <item>United Kingdom</item>
            <item>United States</item>
        </countries>
    </movie>
    <movie id="8108198">
        <top-250-rank>193</top-250-rank>
        <title>Andhadhun</title>
        <runtimes>139</runtimes>
        <year>2018</year>
        <rating>8.3</rating>
        <votes>73515</votes>
        <description>Akash a blind pianist is preparing for a London concert.Sophie's scooter bumps into Akash and upon finding he a pianist she takes him to her restaurant Franco's run by her father and offers him a job.Akash meets 70s actor Pramod Sinha at the restaurant who asks him to do a private concert of his songs at his residence to surprise his wife Simi. Next Day upon reaching his house a shocking surprise is waiting for Akash.</description>
        <cover-url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZWZhMjhhZmYtOTIzOC00MGYzLWI1OGYtM2ZkN2IxNTI4ZWI3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDAzNDk0MTQ@._V1_SY150_CR1,0,101,150_.jpg</cover-url>
        <genres>
            <item>Crime</item>
            <item>Drama</item>
            <item>Music</item>
            <item>Mystery</item>
            <item>Thriller</item>
        </genres>
        <director>
            <person id="1437189">
                <name>Sriram Raghavan</name>
            </person>
        </director>
        <cast>
            <person id="4731677">
                <name>Ayushmann Khurrana</name>
            </person>
            <person id="7102">
                <name>Tabu</name>
            </person>
            <person id="2331000">
                <name>Radhika Apte</name>
            </person>
            <person id="223521">
                <name>Anil Dhawan</name>
            </person>
            <person id="2435847">
                <name>Manav Vij</name>
            </person>
        </cast>
        <countries>
            <item>India</item>
        </countries>
    </movie>
    <movie id="1950186">
        <top-250-rank>200</top-250-rank>
        <title>Ford v Ferrari</title>
        <runtimes>152</runtimes>
        <year>2019</year>
        <rating>8.1</rating>
        <votes>300639</votes>
        <description>As Enzo Ferrari's fast Rosso-Corsa racing cars dominate the mid-1960s motorsport world, the American car designer, Carroll Shelby, is forced to retire after winning the demanding 1959 '24 Hours of Le Mans' endurance race. But, before long, an unexpected proposition by the Vice President of Henry Ford's motor company, Lee Iacocca, will offer an opportunity to beat the Italians at their own game. Now, under those pressing circumstances, the British sports car driver and racing engineer, Ken Miles, reluctantly agrees to lend a hand and improve the firm's image, as Ford's race team has less than ninety days to rewrite history. As a result, the non-conformist duo comes up with the mighty Ford GT40 Mk I high-performance racing car. Can Shelby and Miles break Ferrari's streak?</description>
        <cover-url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BM2UwMDVmMDItM2I2Yi00NGZmLTk4ZTUtY2JjNTQ3OGQ5ZjM2XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTA1OTYzOTUx._V1_SY150_CR0,0,101,150_.jpg</cover-url>
        <genres>
            <item>Action</item>
            <item>Biography</item>
            <item>Drama</item>
            <item>Sport</item>
        </genres>
        <director>
            <person id="3506">
                <name>James Mangold</name>
            </person>
        </director>
        <cast>
            <person id="354">
                <name>Matt Damon</name>
            </person>
            <person id="288">
                <name>Christian Bale</name>
            </person>
            <person id="1256532">
                <name>Jon Bernthal</name>
            </person>
            <person id="1495520">
                <name>Caitriona Balfe</name>
            </person>
            <person id="524197">
                <name>Josh Lucas</name>
            </person>
        </cast>
        <countries>
            <item>United States</item>
        </countries>
    </movie>
    <movie id="7060344">
        <top-250-rank>209</top-250-rank>
        <title>Raatchasan</title>
        <runtimes>170</runtimes>
        <year>2018</year>
        <rating>8.5</rating>
        <votes>26187</votes>
        <description>Circumstances force Arun, an aspiring film director, to take up the job of a Sub Inspector after his father passes away. While Arun faces issues in adjusting to the lifestyle of a police officer, a series of mysterious murders of school going girls happen in the city.</description>
        <cover-url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjU2NzIzMjYtMGE2ZS00YzgzLWE5MzgtZTFiYTlmOWNlYmJkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODIwMDI1NjM@._V1_SY150_CR4,0,101,150_.jpg</cover-url>
        <genres>
            <item>Action</item>
            <item>Crime</item>
            <item>Thriller</item>
        </genres>
        <director>
            <person id="6442107">
                <name>Ram Kumar</name>
            </person>
        </director>
        <cast>
            <person id="3684167">
                <name>Vishnu Vishal</name>
            </person>
            <person id="3898762">
                <name>Amala Paul</name>
            </person>
            <person id="1099597">
                <name>Radha Ravi</name>
            </person>
            <person id="3905156">
                <name>Sangili Murugan</name>
            </person>
            <person id="712437">
                <name>Nizhalgal Ravi</name>
            </person>
        </cast>
        <countries>
            <item>India</item>
        </countries>
    </movie>
    <movie id="2948372">
        <top-250-rank>226</top-250-rank>
        <title>Soul</title>
        <runtimes>100</runtimes>
        <year>2020</year>
        <rating>8.1</rating>
        <votes>201083</votes>
        <description>Joe is a middle-school band teacher whose life hasn't quite gone the way he expected. His true passion is jazz -- and he's good. But when he travels to another realm to help someone find their passion, he soon discovers what it means to have soul.</description>
        <cover-url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZGE1MDg5M2MtNTkyZS00MTY5LTg1YzUtZTlhZmM1Y2EwNmFmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjA3OTI0MDc@._V1_SY150_CR0,0,101,150_.jpg</cover-url>
        <genres>
            <item>Animation</item>
            <item>Adventure</item>
            <item>Comedy</item>
            <item>Family</item>
            <item>Fantasy</item>
            <item>Music</item>
        </genres>
        <director>
            <person id="230032">
                <name>Pete Docter</name>
            </person>
            <person id="5358492">
                <name>Kemp Powers</name>
            </person>
        </director>
        <cast>
            <person id="4937">
                <name>Jamie Foxx</name>
            </person>
            <person id="275486">
                <name>Tina Fey</name>
            </person>
            <person id="636218">
                <name>Graham Norton</name>
            </person>
            <person id="1344302">
                <name>Rachel House</name>
            </person>
            <person id="103797">
                <name>Alice Braga</name>
            </person>
        </cast>
        <countries>
            <item>United States</item>
        </countries>
    </movie>
    <movie id="8613070">
        <top-250-rank>243</top-250-rank>
        <title>Portrait of a Lady on Fire</title>
        <runtimes>122</runtimes>
        <year>2019</year>
        <rating>8.1</rating>
        <votes>66810</votes>
        <description>In 18th century France a young painter, Marianne, is commissioned to do the wedding portrait of Héloïse without her knowing. Therefore, Marianne must observe her model by day to paint her portrait at night. Day by day, the two women become closer as they share Héloïse's last moments of freedom before the impending wedding.</description>
        <cover-url>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjgwNjkwOWYtYmM3My00NzI1LTk5OGItYWY0OTMyZTY4OTg2XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODk4OTc3MTY@._V1_SY150_CR0,0,101,150_.jpg</cover-url>
        <genres>
            <item>Drama</item>
            <item>Romance</item>
        </genres>
        <director>
            <person id="1780037">
                <name>Céline Sciamma</name>
            </person>
        </director>
        <cast>
            <person id="4374524">
                <name>Noémie Merlant</name>
            </person>
            <person id="1194748">
                <name>Adèle Haenel</name>
            </person>
            <person id="4714676">
                <name>Luàna Bajrami</name>
            </person>
            <person id="420">
                <name>Valeria Golino</name>
            </person>
            <person id="1039369">
                <name>Christel Baras</name>
            </person>
        </cast>
        <countries>
            <item>France</item>
        </countries>
    </movie>
</catalog>
